Guide to the Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files 1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989) MS 3009-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Ads (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Direct Mail #4267-4651 (Offsite-box 3609, Folder 1-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1948: General Mail #48-1 - 4-12 (Offsite-box 3609, Folder 6-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1948: General Mail #48-6-B, 48-10-A (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Ads (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Direct Mail #65-319 (Offsite-box 3609, Folder 12-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1949: General Mail #49-1 - 49-6 (Offsite-box 3609, Folder 15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1949: General Mail #49-3-C - 49-10-B (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 8-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1949: General Mail #49-7 - 49-12 (Offsite-box 3610, Folder 1-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Ads (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 10-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Bulletins (Offsite-box 3610, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Direct Mail #12-740 (Offsite-box 3610, Folder 8-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1950: General Mail #50-1 - 50-9 (Offsite-box 3610, Folder 12-16)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1950: General Mail #50-1-A - 50-11-D (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1950: General Mail #50-10 - 50-12 (Offsite-box 3611, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Ads (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Direct Mail #744-1182 (Offsite-box 3611, Folder 4-7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1951: General Mail #51-1 - 51-12 (Offsite-box 3611, Folder 8-12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1951: General Mail #51-8-E - 51-9-D (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Ads (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 16)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3611, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1952: General Mail #52-1 - 52-12 (Offsite-box 3612, Folder 1-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1952: General Mail #52-5-A, 52-8-D (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 17)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Ads (Offsite-box 3639, Folder 18-19)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3612, Folder 9-10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1953: General Mail #53-1 - 53-5-H (Offsite-box 3612, Folder 11-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1953: General Mail #53-4-B - 53-10-H (Offsite-box 3640, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1953: General Mail #53-5-H - 53-11 (Offsite-box 3613, Folder 1-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Ads (Offsite-box 3640, Folder 5-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3613, Folder 7-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1954: General Mail #54-1 - 54-12 (Offsite-box 3613, Folder 9-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1954: General Mail #54-1-A - 54-12-C (Offsite-box 3640, Folder 7-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Ads (Offsite-box 3640, Folder 10-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Counter Displays (Offsite-box 3614, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1954: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3614, Folder 2-3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1955: General Mail #55-1 - 55-12 (Offsite-box 3614, Folder 4-10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1955: General Mail #55-1-A - 55-12-B (Offsite-box 3640, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Ads (Offsite-box 3640, Folder 14-16)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Book, Cards of Identity (Offsite-box 3614, Folder 11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1955: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3614, Folder 12-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1956: General Mail #56-1 - 56-12 (Offsite-box 3615, Folder 1-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1956: General Mail #56-3-D. 56-10-A (Offsite-box 3544, Folder 3-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1956: General Mail #56-4-C - 56-7-A (Offsite-box 3641, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3641, Folder 4-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3615, Folder 10)
  Includes Playbill for the original Broadway production of My Fair Lady featuring Time advertising.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1956: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3615, Folder 11-12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1957: General Mail #57-1 - 57-5 (Offsite-box 3615, Folder 13-15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1957: General Mail #57-1-E - 57-5-D (Offsite-box 3641, Folder 6-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1957: General Mail #57-6 - 57-12 (Offsite-box 3616, Folder 1-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3641, Folder 9-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3616, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1957: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3616, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1958: General Mail #58-1 - 58-6 (Offsite-box 3616, Folder 8-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1958: General Mail #58-1-A - 58-11-D (Offsite-box 3641, Folder 12-15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1958: General Mail #58-7 - 58-12 (Offsite-box 3617, Folder 1-3)
  Includes Enough Time? The Pattern of Executive Life by Eric Hodgins and Alan Dunn, 1959.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3642, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1958: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3517, Folder 4-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1959: General Mail #59-1 - 59-11 (Offsite-box 3517, Folder 6-15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1959: General Mail #59-1-A - 59-9-E (Offsite-box 3642, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1959: General Mail #59-12 (Offsite-box 3618, Folder 1)
  1 phonograph record (33 1/3 rpm); 7 in. flexi disc. On label: "Time for Christmas. Introduction by James A. Linen, Publisher. Time, The Weekly Newsmagazine. Music from Sweden: JUL POTPOURRI, DANSER (Christmas Medley of Dances); Italy: È NATO GESÙ (Jesus was Born); Poland: PRZYSTAPMY DO SZOPY (Hasten to the Manger); Australia: SING GLORIA. By special arrangement with Capitol Records." On container: "Limited Edition Record Enclosed. Five Christmas Carols of Other Lands. Handle with care."
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3642, Folder 6-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3618, Folder 2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3618, Folder 3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1959: Reports (Offsite-box 3618, Folder 4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1960: General Mail #60-1 - 60-7 (Offsite-box 3618, Folder 5-11)
  Includes two Time-branded miniature traffic signs.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1960: General Mail #60-7-C - 60-12 (Offsite-box 3619, Folder 1-10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1960: General Mail #60-1-B - 60-11-B (Offsite-box 3642, Folder 9-10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3642, Folder 11-12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3619, Folder 11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1960: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3619, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1961: General Mail #61-1 - 61-2 (Offsite-box 3619, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1961: General Mail #61-3 - 61-12 (Offsite-box 3620, Folder 1-12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1961: General Mail #61-12-B (Offsite-box 3643, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1961: General Mail #61-12-B (Offsite-box 3642, Folder 13-15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3643, Folder 3-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3620, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1961: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3621, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1962: General Mail #62-1-A, 62-6-A (Offsite-box 3643, Folder 6-7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1962: General Mail #62-2 - 62-10 (Offsite-box 3621, Folder 2-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1962: General Mail #62-10 - 62-12 (Offsite-box 3622, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3643, Folder 8-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3622, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Dansk Finnish Linen (Offsite-box 3622, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1962: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3622, Folder 7-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: General Mail #63-1 - 63-3 (Offsite-box 3622, Folder 9-12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: General Mail #63-2-A - 63-10-C (Offsite-box 3643, Folder 10-12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: General Mail #63-3 - 63-10 (Offsite-box 3623, Folder 1-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: General Mail #63-11 - 63-12 (Offsite-box 3624, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3643, Folder 13-15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3624, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: Direct Mail and Outserts (Offsite-box 3624, Folder 6-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1963: "The Passing Parade" Presentation for Eli Lilly and Company, circa 1963 (Offsite-box 3544, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1964: General Mail #64-1 - 64-4-B (Offsite-box 3624, Folder 9-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1964: General Mail #64-4-C - 64-10 (Offsite-box 3625, Folder 1-12)
  Includes two Time-branded newsstand paperweights.
  Includes two sets of eight reproduction Independence Day postcards as part of a Fourth of July promotion package.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1964: General Mail #64-10 - 64-12 (Offsite-box 3626, Folder 1-4)
  Includes two silk handkerchief maps of the L'Enfant Plan. Based on the engraving Plan of the City of Washington in the Territory of Columbia ceded by the States of Virginia and Maryland to the United States of America and by them established as the Seat of their Government after the year MDCCC by Samuel Hill, from the Library of Congress.
  Enclosed with booklet. On cover: "L'Enfant's Plan of the City of Washington, 1792, presented by Time, The Weekly Newsmagazine in token of the opening of the 89th Congress, January 4, 1965." On page 1: "'Handkerchief' map with decorative corners."
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3644, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3626, Folder 5-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Direct Mail and Outserts (Offsite-box 3626, Folder 7-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1964: "Story Behind the Story" (Offsite-box 3626, Folder 10-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: General Mail #65-1 - 65-3 (Offsite-box 3626, Folder 12-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: General Mail #65-4 - 65-12-B (Offsite-box 3627, Folder 1-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: General Mail #65-4-D - 65-6 (Offsite-box 3644, Folder 5-6)
  Includes information booklet included with set of 14 picnic plates in red, white and blue, in various stars and stripes designs, as part of a Fourth of July promotion package. The plates themselves are not present in this collection.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: General Mail #65-12-C (Offsite-box 3628, Folder 1-3)
  Includes Time Essay: Issues, trends, problems of our day - a selection from the Essay department of TIME The Weekly Newsmagazine by the Editors of Time, 1965.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3644, Folder 7-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3628, Folder 4-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Direct Mail and Outserts (Offsite-box 3628, Folder 6-8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1965: "Story Behind the Story" (Offsite-box 3628, Folder 9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1966: General Mail #66-1 - 66-7 (Offsite-box 3628, Folder 10-15)
  Includes a folio of sheet music of four American Revolutionary songs, including "The Liberty Song," "What a Court Hath Old England," "Yankee Doodle," and "Ode for American Independence," as part of a Fourth of July promotion package.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1966: General Mail #66-3-C (Offsite-box 3644, Folder 10-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1966: General Mail #66-8 - 66-12 (Offsite-box 3629, Folder 1-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3644, Folder 12-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3629, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Direct Mail and Outserts (Offsite-box 3629, Folder 8)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1967: General Mail #67-1 - 67-7 (Offsite-box 3629, Folder 9-13)
  Includes Time-branded paper dress for Valentine's Day.
  Includes five sets of six reproduction American Colonial-era coins as part of a Fourth of July promotion package.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1967: General Mail #67-2-D (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1967: General Mail #67-8 - 67-12 (Offsite-box 3630, Folder 1-9)
  Includes Time Capsule/1941: A History of the Year Condensed from the Pages of Time, 1967.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 3-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Ads: "Missing I" Campaign (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3630, Folder 10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1968: General Mail #68-1 - 68-6-A (Offsite-box 3630, Folder 11-14)
  Includes Election Watcher's Companion 1968, 1968.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1968: General Mail #68-6-A - 68-12 (Offsite-box 3631, Folder 1-11)
  Includes five sets of three paper lanterns modeled after 19th century political campaign lanterns as part of a Fourth of July promotion package. Designs include the Statue of Liberty with the phrase "To the polls, ye sons of liberty"; an illustration of a bald eagle with the Constitution and the Liberty Bell; and the phrase "Union Forever" on stars and stripes.
  On label: "The lanterns enclosed are modeled on those which in the 19th Century were emblazoned with political slogans or portraits of the candidates."
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1968: General Mail #68-6-B (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 6-7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 8-9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3631, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Direct Mail (Offsite-box 3631, Folder 13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1969: General Mail #69-1 - 69-2 (Offsite-box 3631, Folder 14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1969: General Mail #69-3 - 69-9 (Offsite-box 3632, Folder 1-13)
  Includes two sets of reproduction pewter military buttons from the American Revolutionary War as part of a Fourth of July promotion package.
  On label: "These military Buttons are Recastings in Pewter from the Originals found at the Revolutionary Redoubts near West Point - the larger made for the Continental Artillery in 1775, the smaller a New York regimental Design."
  Includes two sets of fifty Time-branded cocktail napkins.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1969: General Mail #69-10 - 69-12 (Offsite-box 3633, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 10-11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3633, Folder 3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1970: General Mail #70-1 - 70-12 (Offsite-box 3633, Folder 4-13)
  Includes Time "Woman of the Year" mirror for Valentine's Day.
  Include red kite as part of a Fourth of July promotion package.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1970: General Mail #70-5-B (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3645, Folder 13-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3634, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1971: General Mail #71-1 - 71-12 (Offsite-box 3634, Folder 2-9)
  Includes four sets of nine red, white and blue jumbo graphite pencils branded with the Time logo as part of a Fourth of July promotion package.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 1-6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Ads: Small Space (Offsite-box 3634, Folder 10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1971-1973: Environment Package (Offsite-box 3634, Folder 11-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1972: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1972: General Mail #72-1-A (Offsite-box 3634, Folder 14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1972: General Mail #72-1-B - 72-12 (Offsite-box 3635, Folder 1-14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1973: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 8-10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1973: General Mail #73-1 - 73-7 (Offsite-box 3636, Folder 1-11)
  Includes letterpress plate in wooden block featuring an excerpt from the First Amendment to the US Constitution as part of a Fourth of July promotion package.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1973: General Mail #73-7 - 73-12 (Offsite-box 3637, Folder 1-8)
  Includes seven copies of a gold coin commemorating the fiftieth anniversary of Time, featuring busts of Briton Hadden and Henry Luce on the obverse and the "Time 50" logo on the reverse. Two versions were sent to sales representatives and staff.
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1974: General (Offsite-box 3637, Folder 9)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1974: General Mail #74-6 (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 11)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1976: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 12)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1978: General (Offsite-box 3637, Folder 10)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1982-1984: General (Offsite-box 3637, Folder 11-13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1983: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 13)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1984: Dear Editor: Letters to Time Magazine, 1923-1984 (Offsite-box 3637, Folder 14)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1985-1989: General (Offsite-box 3637, Folder 15-19)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1985-1986: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 14-15)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1988: Cover Subjects (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 16)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1990: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 17)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1991: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3544, Folder 6)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1992: Ads: General (Offsite-box 3544, Folder 7)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: 1993: General (Offsite-box 3646, Folder 18)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Campaigns, 1955 (Offsite-box 3647, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Contests: Circulation Letter Sweepstakes, 1955 (Offsite-box 3647, Folder 2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Contests: "As Seen By", 1957 (Offsite-box 3647, Folder 3-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Contests: "Finish the Letter", 1957 (Offsite-box 3648, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Direct Mail, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 3648, Folder 3-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Direct Mail, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3649, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Direct Mail, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3650, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Direct Mail, 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 3651, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Magazine Advertising, 1959 (Offsite-box 3652, Folder 1)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Newspaper Advertising, 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 3652, Folder 2-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Newspaper Advertising, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 3653, Folder 1-5)
- Time: Advertising Promotion: Promotion Notebooks: Trade Advertising, 1952-1958 (Offsite-box 3654, Folder 1-6)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: House Ads and Inserts, 1923-1959 (Offsite-box 3655, Folder 1-7)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: House Ads and Inserts, 1923-1962 (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 1-5)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Inserts, 1951-1975 (Offsite-box 3655, Folder 8-32)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Inserts, 1976, circa 1950s (Offsite-box 3656, Folder 1-2)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Newsstand Banner, 1952 (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 16)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Space Ads and Inserts, 1923-1971 (Offsite-box 3656, Folder 3-18)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Space Ads and Inserts, 1926, 1937-1938, 1959-1967 (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 6-15)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: "Take-one" Posters, circa 1960s (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 17)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Club Bureau, 1927-1940 (Offsite-box 3656, Folder 19-20)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Cooperative Mailings: Department Stores, 1947-1953 (Offsite-box 3656, Folder 21)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1923-1971 (Offsite-box 3656, Folder 22-35)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1972-1974 (Offsite-box 3657, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1923-1949 (Offsite-box 3657, Folder 4-18)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1948-1965 (Offsite-box 3658, Folder 1-20)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1966-1974 (Offsite-box 3659, Folder 1-8)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1923-1947 (Offsite-box 3659, Folder 9-22)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1948-1955 (Offsite-box 3660, Folder 1-17)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1955-1966 (Offsite-box 3661, Folder 1-19)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1967-1974, 1979 (Offsite-box 3662, Folder 1-14)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1930-1940 (Offsite-box 3662, Folder 15-17)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1940-1949 (Offsite-box 3663, Folder 1-17)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1950-1968 (Offsite-box 3664, Folder 1-23)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1968, 1992 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Specials: American Art Book: Direct Mail, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 4)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Specials: American Art Book: House Ads and Inserts, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 5)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Specials: American Art Book: Space Ads and Inserts, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 6)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Specials: American Art Book: Miscellaneous Promotion, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 7)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Specials: Historic Events Campaign: House and Space Ads, 1923-1930 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 8)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Specials: Historic Events Campaign: House and Space Ads, 1923-1930 (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 18)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Specials: Miscellaneous Mailings, 1941, 1952-1956, 1964 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 9)
- Time: Circulation Promotion: Stamps Index, circa 1971 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 10)
- Time: Education Department: College Bureau: General, 1951-1955 (Offsite-box 3665, Folder 11-22)
- Time: Education Department: College Bureau: General, 1952-1961 (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 19-29)
- Time: Education Department: College Bureau: General, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 3666, Folder 1-17)
- Time: Education Department: College Bureau: General, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 3667, Folder 1-14)
- Time: Education Department: College Bureau: General, 1963 (Offsite-box 3668, Folder 1-4)
- Time: Education Department: College Bureau: College Store Journal Ads, 1964-1968 (Offsite-box 3691, Folder 30)
- Time: Education Department: College Bureau: Samplings, 1979-1981 (Offsite-box 3668, Folder 5)
- Time: Education Department: Cover Quiz, 1953-1959 (Offsite-box 3668, Folder 6)
- Time: Education Department: Current Affairs Tests, 1934-1969 (Offsite-box 3668, Folder 7-15)
- Time: Education Department: Current Affairs Tests, 1960-1989 (Offsite-box 3669, Folder 1-3)
- Time: Education Department: Michigan Educators, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 3669, Folder 4-5)
- Time: Education Department: Monthly News Quiz, 1954-1965 (Offsite-box 3669, Folder 6-7)